[
  {
    "question": "In the 1960s, many environmental artists began to view their art as a(n)",
    "a": "mirror",
    "b": "ecosystem",
    "c": "instrument",
    "d": "experiment",
    "e": "dialogue",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a common theme throughout Helen and Newton Harrison’s career?",
    "a": "Their artwork critiqued consumerism and capitalism.",
    "b": "Their artwork examined the intersection of technology and nature.",
    "c": "Their artwork had a tangible impact on the environment.",
    "d": "Their artwork experimented with multi-media installations.",
    "e": "Their artwork celebrated indigenous cultures.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Shrimp Farm differ from previous environmental artworks?",
    "a": "It incorporated cutting-edge digital technology.",
    "b": "It interjected fictional narratives into real-world ecosystems.",
    "c": "It relied on consultation from environmental scientists and researchers.",
    "d": "It explored abstract concepts of time and space.",
    "e": "It consciously involved the interactivity of the ecosystems.",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which series of artworks by the Harrisons marked their shift from focusing on closed living systems to open ones?",
    "a": "Baltimore Promenade",
    "b": "Survival Pieces",
    "c": "Serpentine Lattice",
    "d": "Making Earth",
    "e": "The Lagoon Cycle",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hans Haacke played a critical role in all of the following contemporary art movements EXCEPT",
    "a": "Land art",
    "b": "conceptual art",
    "c": "video art",
    "d": "institutional critique",
    "e": "kinetic art",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Haacke engage with the idea of ecological systems in his earlier works like Condensation Cube?",
    "a": "by simulating weather systems with real-time data feeds",
    "b": "by creating soundscapes that were integral to the artworks",
    "c": "by integrating mechanical systems into kinetic sculptures",
    "d": "by enclosing systems within the material of his artwork",
    "e": "by using statistical data to illustrate economic systems",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following issues did Haacke address in Rhine Water Purification Plant?",
    "a": "political corruption",
    "b": "technological progress",
    "c": "urban infrastructure",
    "d": "cultural appropriation",
    "e": "economic inequality",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sun Tunnels explored all of the following concepts EXCEPT",
    "a": "the deep time of light that travels from the stars",
    "b": "daily sunrises and sunsets",
    "c": "ancient geological time of the American West",
    "d": "the Earth’s annual orbit around the Sun",
    "e": "circadian rhythms and biological cycles",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Holt’s later works like Dark Star Parks reflect her sustained commitment to",
    "a": "collaborating with scientists and researchers",
    "b": "working with communities",
    "c": "challenging traditional notions of art",
    "d": "addressing socioeconomic issues",
    "e": "experimenting with new media",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mark Dion’s career reflects an interest in",
    "a": "the aesthetics of urban decay",
    "b": "the techniques of museum displays",
    "c": "the taxonomy of rare species",
    "d": "the sociology of public spaces",
    "e": "the evolution of natural history",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which natural historian inspired Dion to create A Meter of Jungle?",
    "a": "Jacques Cousteau",
    "b": "Aldo Leopold",
    "c": "David Attenborough",
    "d": "William Beebe",
    "e": "Rachel Carson",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dion created A Meter of Jungle to explore the issue of",
    "a": "soil erosion in Panama",
    "b": "biodiversity loss in Madagascar",
    "c": "unsustainable agricultural practices in Australia",
    "d": "illegal poaching in Indonesia",
    "e": "deforestation in Brazil",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pierre Huyghe’s art often blurs the boundary between",
    "a": "high art and popular culture",
    "b": "artistic creations and real life",
    "c": "tradition and innovation",
    "d": "art and science",
    "e": "individual and collective identity",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which open-source project did Huyghe create through co-authorship with many artists?",
    "a": "Amarillo Ramp",
    "b": "No Ghost Just a Shell",
    "c": "Tropical Rainforest Preserves",
    "d": "Untilled",
    "e": "The Third Memory",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Untilled represent a turning point in Huyghe’s career?",
    "a": "It marks a shift towards producing contemporary eco art.",
    "b": "It showcases newfound experimentation with kinetic sculptures.",
    "c": "It demonstrates a transition towards large-scale public art projects.",
    "d": "It reflects a transition towards abstract expressionism.",
    "e": "It signifies a shift towards interactive digital installations.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  }
]